The bride collapsed during her ceremony,
blood dribbling from her mouth.
Doesn't your wife's champagne look odd?
She was poisoned?
Could you please assist me, Sakuraba?
I won't forgive whoever harmed my wife.
All attendees of the wedding are suspects.
Truth be told, I actually have one lead.
A lead?
The day before our ceremony...
this letter was left in our mailbox.
[Unhappiest wishes to you, Red Riding Hood]
[Red Riding Hood]
An anonymous threat?
I see you two are getting along.
Sorry.
Who is this "Red Riding Hood"?
I have no idea.
What is this a picture of?
Not sure, but that's a person on the left.
Did you ask Sayaka about these?
Yeah. She was just as lost as I was.
If anything, she was terrified.
You suspect one of your wedding guests
sent this letter, correct?
First, there are both your parents.
Then there are the bride's friends
from high school, Chie and Airi.
Finally, there are your guests.
Your friends from university, Sugiura -
I won't believe it.
What?
They're all good people, alright?
There's no way one of them is the culprit.
Then we're done here?
No, no.
I'll push through.
For Sayaka's sake.
I will find the culprit.
How did you first meet Sayaka?
This guy, Makoto,
introduced us a year ago.
He said she was a friend of a friend.
She was a shy girl.
But she was equally as kind.
I went on several dates with her.
But last autumn,
I noticed she wasn't acting like herself.
She took leave from her work at a patisserie,
and began seeing a therapist.
Why?
She was being harassed online.
Negative reviews directed at her
were being posted on foodie sites.
[Female, 20's, had terrible customer service]
"Terrible customer service".
They were being posted everywhere.
Eventually, the owner of that patisserie
pressured her to quit.
If you continue to take days off...
That man offered her no support.
He only backed her into a corner.
I couldn't believe what I was hearing.
Wait, you were there when it happened?
Yeah.
I sat at a table a little distance away,
since we weren't officially a couple yet.
After the owner left, Sayaka cried.
That's when I knew.
I was going to protect her.
I wanted to protect her.
Which eventually led to marriage.
I knew she was the only one for me.
Sayaka was eager to marry as well.
You're a kind man, Hayashida.
Well...
Men are duty bound
to protect the women they love.
A certain principle
fuels his passion for her.
Would people call him an honorable man? Or...
Evening, Sakuraba.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
Good evening.
Here's my offering for today.
Thank you.
Where's Sachiko?
She's over there.
You had a friend over? Hello there.
Sachiko? Where are you, dear?
Is that your... girlfriend?
What?
I mean, she barged in with a spare key.
That's Mrs. Yonemura.
She's a fellow cat lover
who comes to care for Sachiko.
Your cat's name is "Sachiko"?
Yes?
Odd name.
You think? Sachiko is a girl's name.
What's so odd about it?
Right, before I forget.
I wanted to ask.
How do you read this first name of yours?
It's read, "Sapphire".
My name is Sapphire Sakuraba.
S-Sapphire?
Oh my, isn't that Kaori's daughter?
You know Sayaka?
Right, Sayaka! What a familiar face.
Our families used to be neighbors.
Wow, she's become an absolute beauty.
And you're her husband?
Yes, I am.
Gosh, what a small world!
Isn't that right, Sachiko?
I remember Sayaka and her violin.
Kaori always boasted about her playing.
If only she didn't get hurt...
Hurt?
She fractured her left arm
in elementary school.
Yes. She could no longer pursue
a professional career in violin.
What happened afterwards
was especially a pity.
Pardon?
Oh, look at me blabbering again.
Gosh, it's already 7.
I have to get home and feed my own kitties.
I'll visit again.
Say...
Aren't you...
Getting hungry? Yes.
How about you, Sachiko?
That was delicious.
Thanks for the food.
Hayashida.
There's something I want to confirm with you.
Does the champagne here look normal to you?
Yeah.
In other words, this is the "before".
And this, is the "after".
It's gotten darker.
That's right.
Come here.
The before was taken at 3:45PM.
[3:45PM]
The after, at 3:50PM.
Only five minutes later.
I see. Someone poisoned her in that time.
Thank you.
I have no picture of Sayaka's glass
in this five minute window.
But I can identify the individuals
who had access to her drink.
First, sitting to her left
was the groom, Hayashida.
You could have easily poisoned her drink.
Hey.
Why would I do that?
Next, sitting to her right
was the bride's mother, Kaori.
Her mother is also innocent.
You think so?
Sayaka is her daughter.
She wouldn't poison her own child.
Then that leaves two suspects.
Mr. Photographer.
Could you get a shot of us?
Sure thing.
Sayaka's friends from high school.
Airi, and Chie.
You're saying one of them...
poisoned Sayaka?
[Chie: Can we talk?]
I apologize if this seemed so sudden.
It's fine.
I'm glad I asked Sayaka for your number.
I...
I still can't believe what happened
at the wedding.
I haven't been able to sleep
because of the shock.
I had no idea.
I'm sorry for the trouble we've caused you.
Don't apologize, Kazuomi.
It's not your fault.
Sayaka is a dear friend. Of course I'd worry.
Right.
Thank you.
Sayaka's a lucky girl.
Where did she find a kind,
handsome man like you?
You give me too much credit.
I wish I had the same luck as she did.
I broke up with my boyfriend just last month.
What?
He was cheating on me.
I see...
[Sakuraba: Get to the point already.]
Well... in any case...
What was it you wanted to discuss with me?
Right.
Kazuomi.
Have you gone to get an exorcism?
- Pardon?
- You should really go.
I bet some evil spirit affected your wedding.
You have to get rid of it!
I-Is that so...
I know a spiritualist who can help.
They can see guardian spirits, too.
Don't worry,
they won't sell you anything weird.
I see.
Don't worry, it'll wash out.
I'm so sorry.
If you'll give me a moment.
Hey, what's the big idea?
You were being sold on a scheme.
I was not.
We're getting off track.
You need to figure out if she's guilty.
I can't just ask her if she poisoned Sayaka.
Then pinpoint a motive first.
Maybe she has something against Sayaka.
A motive...
Sorry, did anything get stained?
Nope. When should I schedule the exorcism?
Well, erm...
Chie.
What do you think of Sayaka?
Huh? Why ask?
I, uh... got curious.
She's my best friend.
Wasn't that obvious?
She's a bit timid, and faint-hearted.
But that's part of why I like her.
She could never do anything alone.
She needed someone at her side.
Indeed.
I worried for her
when we graduated high school.
Especially with her juggling culinary school,
and her job at the ConCafe.
ConCafe?
[T/N: a themed cafe, like a maid cafe]
Sayaka worked at a ConCafe?
Never mind. Please forget I said that.
Like, one of those concept cafes?
That's practically like working the nightlife.
Please don't misunderstand.
Sayaka had her reasons.
She had to pay her own tuition and rent,
without any support from her parents.
She had to work a profitable job.
If it's of any solace,
Sayaka never wore anything risqué.
She avoided the nurse and animal cosplays.
She always dressed as Little Red Riding Hood.
[Unhappiest wishes to you, Red Riding Hood]
What a downpour!
We're not even close to the station.
Far from it, really.
You and Sayaka live in the area, right?
Sayaka promised to invite me over
after the wedding.
Is that so.
I'm absolutely soaked.
[Hayashida!]
[Get a grip!]
[She's a suspect!]
[Call ended]
Seriously?
Here, if you needed a change of clothes.
They're Sayaka's.
No, I couldn't trouble you further.
I'll brew us some warm tea.
You won't be changing?
No, I feel bad about borrowing clothes.
It's really no big deal.
Kazuomi.
Yes?
Your hands.
Could I see them?
My hands?
I can read palms.
It's a specialty of mine.
I knew it. You do have a heart of gold.
You also have a strong sense of justice.
You take action for the sake of others.
I think that's wonderful.
There you go.
Why did you hang up?
You suddenly bombarded me with texts.
I'm freezing...
Is everything alright?
Yes, fine.
She was getting suspicious.
So you brought her here.
I'm ashamed I doubted her for even a second.
I think that's wonderful.
Chie.
Yes?
Thank you.
Sayaka has such wonderful friends.
Kazuomi.
Thank you for marrying Sayaka.
Huh?
Sayaka's my best friend.
Let me know if you ever need my help, okay?
I would do anything for Sayaka.
Chie wasn't suspicious after all.
Hayashida. You're absolutely useless.
What? Rude.
We're looking for the individual
who poisoned your wife.
And she's one of our suspects.
You'd get it if you spoke to her, Sakuraba.
She thanked me for marrying Sayaka.
Only a true friend would say that.
That's not a blessing people give,
friend or otherwise.
If anything, it seems rather condescending.
That was no slip of the tongue.
And neither was her mentioning the ConCafe.
But you knew about the job, didn't you?
Of course not.
This isn't getting anywhere.
Let's switch topics.
The other day,
you mentioned Sayaka was harassed
on food review sites.
Right.
After looking into it a bit further,
those reviews led me to a certain individual.
[Me and the bestie, Sayaka]
She's the most suspicious one yet.
Airi?
[Me and the bestie, Sayaka]